savefront.com 2016-10-28

# SaveFront - Best Deals On All Fronts

Home / Privacy Policy

## Privacy Policy

SaveFront (“We” or “Us”) provides this Privacy Policy to inform you of our policies and procedures regarding the collection, use and disclosure of personal information we receive when you visit [www.savefront.com](http://www.savefront.com/) (the “Site”) and when you use any part of our service or software via our Site or on the websites of our partners or other third parties (collectively, the “Service”). This Privacy Policy applies only to information that you provide to us when you access or use any information, services, products or content appearing on the Site or offered by us through the Service. It does not apply to information we have obtained offline or through other traditional means. This Privacy Policy may be amended or updated from time to time. If we make any material changes to this Privacy Policy, we will post a notice of these changes on the Site and in this Privacy Policy. You are advised to consult this Privacy Policy regularly for any changes. 

**1\. Information Collection**  
The Site contains links to websites of third parties. We are not responsible for the actions of these third parties, including their privacy practices and any content posted on their websites. We encourage you to review their privacy policies to learn more about what, why and how they collect and use Personal Information. 

_Non-Personally Identifiable Information._

When you access the Site or use the Service, (whether such use is performed on the Site or on a website of one of our partners or other third parties), we collect the following non-personally identifiable information (“ **Non-Personal Information** ”): 

  * Information regarding your use of the Service;
  * Information that your browser sends whenever you visit a website or online service (“Log Data”). This Log Data may include, but is not limited to, your computer’s Internet Protocol address, language, browser type, location, time zone, unique device identifier, the web page you were visiting before you came to the Site and information you search for on the Site and through the Service
  * Like many websites, we use “Web cookies” and “Adobe Flash Local Shared Objects” to collect information. A cookie is a small data file that we transfer to your computer’s hard disk for record-keeping purposes. We use “session ID cookies” to enable certain features of the Services, to better understand how you interact with the Services and to monitor web traffic routing on the Site and aggregate usage of the Services. You can instruct your browser, by changing its options, to stop accepting cookies or to prompt you before accepting a cookie from the website you visit. If you do not accept cookies, however, you may not be able to use all portions of the Site or all functionality of the Services
  * Third party websites which may advertise on the Site and other third parties that you interact with through your use of the Service may also place or read cookies on your computer’s browser, which enables them to collect information about users who view or interact with their advertisements and content. The collection and use of such information and access of any third party websites are subject to such third party’s privacy policy. If Personal Information is integrated with Non-Personal Information, we will regard the integrated information as Personal Information for as long as such information remains integrated. 

_Links and Third Party Sites_

The Site may contain links in a format that enables Us to keep track of whether you have followed them. Furthermore, the Services and Site may contain information in the form of, but not limited to, articles, advertisements, third-party opinions and links to third party websites – all which are not owned or controlled by Us. Such information is provided by Us as a convenience to our users and visitors and as such, We assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies, or practices of any third party. While we do not transfer any information to such third parties (whether Personally Identifiable Information, Non-Personally Identifiable Information or otherwise), you should be aware that this Privacy Policy applies only to the Service. We do not exercise control over the sites that provide Content, ranking or other information, or over banners, other advertisements or links from within the Site or the Service. These other sites may place their own cookies or other files on your computer, collect data or solicit personal information from you. Other websites follow different rules regarding the use or disclosure of the Personal Information that you submit. We encourage you to read the privacy policies and other terms of the other websites as we do not have any control or liability over such practices. Whenever you connect with a third party application or website, we might receive information from them, including information about actions you take. 

**2\. Our Policy Toward Children**  
We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 13 without the consent of the parent or guardian. If a parent or guardian becomes aware that his or her child has provided us with Personal Information without their consent, he or she should contact us at support@savefront.com If we become aware that a child under 13 has provided us with Personal Information, we will delete such information from our files. 

**3\. How We Use Non-Personal Information**  
We use Non-Personal Information for the above purposes and in order to (i) monitor and analyze use of the Service and for the technical administration of the Site, (ii) improve the Site and the Service, (iii) generate and derive useful data and information concerning the interests, characteristics and website use behavior of our users, and (iv) verify that visitors and users to the Site and of the Services meet the criteria required to process their requests. 

_In addition, we may post ancillary privacy notices with respect to specific services._

**4\. Information Sharing and Disclosure**

  * Submissions. Any information you choose to provide in an application, a comment or a submission should reflect how much you want other users to know about you. We recommend that you guard your anonymity and sensitive information and we encourage users to think carefully about what information they disclose in their applications, comments or submissions.
  * Aggregate Information and Non-Personal Information. We may share aggregated information, including reports generated as a result of your use of the Service, that includes Non-Personal Information and log data with third parties for industry analysis, demographic profiling, other commercial purposes and to deliver targeted advertising about other products and services. Any aggregated information shared in these contexts will not contain your Personal Information.
  * Service Providers. We may employ third party companies and individuals to facilitate the Service, to provide the Service on our behalf and to perform services related to administration of the Service or the Site (including, without limitation, maintenance, hosting and database management services, web analytics and administration). Compliance with Laws and Law Enforcement. We cooperate with government and law enforcement officials and private parties to enforce and comply with the law. We will disclose any information about you to government or law enforcement officials or private parties as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate to respond to claims and legal process (including but not limited to subpoenas), to protect our or a third party’s property and rights, to protect the safety of the public or any person, or to prevent or stop any activity we may consider to be, or to pose a risk of being, illegal, unethical, inappropriate or legally actionable.
  * Content Analysis. We reserve the right to analyze your Content and its use by users on the Platform for any purpose, including commercial (such as for targeting the delivery of advertisements and indexing content for search).

**6\. Security**  
We are concerned with safeguarding your information. We employ a variety of measures designed to protect your information from unauthorized access and disclosure. 

**7\. International Processing or Transfer**  
Your information may be processed or transferred outside of your state, where the privacy laws may not be as protective as those in your jurisdiction. 

**8\. Contacting Us**  
If you have any concerns or questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at [support@savefront.com](mailto:support@savefront.com)  
Copyright © 2012 SaveFront. All rights reserved.
